{
    "id": "3389d17ac99e453e8e6f76f4e81ca22e",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The proofreader looked .............................. the document carefully.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8753bf1e8a7747e9b67b4c04f0b19950"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look ...................................... unfamiliar words in a dictionary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "at",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b9c80f9be9554b4dbc4bdaf53632ecaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "When asked why he was absent he made ...................................... a story about being ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e277daaa2ff436fb606ef54ad406e95"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldnâ€™t make ..................................... anything that she said.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d2cf0c5a57104ecab1a435b2ddc2c48d"
        },
        {
            "question": "A crane was used to pick .................................... the bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "acc353628ab541569ebe7785d24e3f07"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of the grammar software out there can point ................................. all the grammar mistakes in a piece of writing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f3bb7311f8c4ba3ac96c8702eaa6ae7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must put ..................................... some money for your retirement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a0f5e21a3894b63817611c2f11e75ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will have to put ................................... the meeting until Wednesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4654e5ad3bb248f5b46acbf92dfaa87d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is in his room putting ..................................... his shoes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "88bd5da969a04ef0b75e15c3f0733428"
        },
        {
            "question": "The firemen could not put ................................... the fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cab71d803e28420e9f33bfa2615528e6"
        }
    ]
}